Brother-in-law
Шурин
This is the invitation
Это приглашение которое генерал
The general asked me to bring
передал мне чтобы я доставил тебе
The general hasn't returned
Генерал несколько лет
To the capital these years
не возвращался в столицу
Who to see
Чтобы никто не гадал кого он хочет видеть
Who not to see
кого нет
Seeing first
кого первым
Or later
а кого позже
He's afraid people will think too much
он боится что люди будут слишком много думать
So
поэтому
He's simply holding a banquet
просто устроит пир
All at once
за один раз
To see everyone he needs to see
встретится со всеми с кем нужно
I delivered it home immediately
Я первым делом принёс его домой
Brother-in-law
Шурин
You're definitely the first person
ты точно первый во всей столице
In the entire capital to receive the invitation
кто получил это приглашение
You need to prepare well
так что готовься как следует
Forgot
Ай я забыл
I need to hurry off
Надо спешить
Still need to deliver to the next house
ещё другим людям не передал
Sister
Сестра
Brother-in-law
шурин
No need to see me off
не провожайте
Haven't finished eating yet
Но ты же ещё не доел
Eat on the way
Поем на ходу
Who's the blind one
Кто это там посмел
Daring to block my way?
встать мне поперёк дороги
Deserves a beating
Получай
I wasn't paying attention just now
Только сейчас не заметил
Again
давай по новой
Look at his temper
Только посмотри на его характер